If you're looking for a high quality, reliable
video editor, I would highly recommend working
with Tayyab.
I run a YouTube channel with over 60,000 subscribers
and Tayyab has been a complete game changer for
me and my channel.
The very first video he edited for me got over
100,000 views and I've worked with
a bunch of video editors in the past and none
of them have been consistent or been able to
get me high quality edits in a reasonable amount
of time consistently.
And Tayyab has been able to do just that.
He was able to follow my instructions and not
only match my personal video editing style
, but improve upon it.
And thanks to him, I've been able to divert
my attention to other parts of my business
because I know that I can trust him to handle
the video editing.
And he's by far the best video editor that
I have ever worked with in my three or four
years since starting my YouTube channel.
So I would highly recommend working with him
if you are lucky enough to do so.